This is strange.
Illogical, even.
Whoever the enemy is, they're
using a stand right now.
I can clearly feel its presence.
But for some reason, the
stand user isn't in this town.
I can even sense them moving further away.
away.
If they were going to launch an attack
on us, they'd have to move closer.
What does this mean?
There it is.
Come back here, body.
If the enemy's smart,
they'll try to assassinate
me while I'm vulnerable without my stand.
My top priority is protecting my body.
What the heck is he doing?
Thank you.
Let's go.
Yo!
Look, it's Batman!
Batman's right up there!
Frickin' sweet!
Damn it.
Why won't my body just stay still?
Where is it even going?
Why can't you see me right
in front of you, Weather?
Could it be because you're
not affected by its power?
You can leave finding
my body to me, Weather.
Just go after the enemy stand, user.
Anastasia, where did you go?
You cocky bastard!
How dare you waltz back over
here after what you did!
Stay put!
I'm calling the police!
Hello, yes?
I need some officers here.
Hey, hold on.
By any chance, were you talking to me?
Shut your mouth and get the
hell away from my store!
Relax, man. Is this enough?
I'm in a hurry, but I'm in
need of some information.
Not even close!
Look what you did to
my store, you lunatic!
It's not like I have a wife
to run this place with me!
Wait, what?
Are you saying I've been in here already?
If you need more money,
I'll give you more.
I'll pay whatever.
So please hang up the phone, all right?
Now which way did he go?
Hurry and tell me!
Huh?
Oh, uh, right.
The guy who came in here
before was my twin brother.
What's going on over here?
Is there some kind of problem?
This is Unit 6.
We have located a man who closely matches
the description of the escaped convict.
Roger that.
Excuse me, sir.
Would you turn around and face us, please?
That's me!
My body was still in the fucking
chocolate shop that whole time?!
I asked you to turn around.
We just need you to answer some questions.
Now show us your face.
There ain't no problem here.
See you, officer.
Mm-hmm.
I'm sorry, sir.
Huh?
Where did that old man run off to?
Diver, drive.
I implanted chocolates
under the skin of my face.
Coming to you with an update.
We have received word that
the character Kenshiro
from one of Japan's many
popular animated series?
has defeated the evil Rao in
the streets of East Shinjuku.
It is an incident that reflects exactly
what happens in the original story.
Hey, where are you hiding?
Come out right now! Yay! Hooray!
The princess has awakened!
Our lovely Snow White
has finally woken up!
The geezer from the chocolate shop?
Hey there!
Did you find your story?
I'm tired of being old and alone.
I don't need my body anymore.
My last days will be spent to
Snow White's Prince Charming!
It's my greatest Dream Country!
It's just like the story!
Just like the story!
Like the story? Again?
You bastard!
How dare you do this to me?
How dare you?
I'm going to make you pay for
devouring my brothers, you asshole!
What the shit is that thing?
Did these things come out of the
chocolates I used in my face?
Are they goats or pieces of chocolate?
In the story he's very devious
the sly wolf managed to trick
the seven young goats and entered
their house and once he was
inside the ferocious fur monster
went around capturing and devouring
the young goats one by one the
only one that survived was the
youngest goat and only because
he hid in the old grandfather
clock this story I know this one
the mother of the young goats came
back home to the slaughter and
was very angry upon finding the
big bad wolf she She took the
scissors and sliced his stomach open.
Snip, snip!
She dragged out his intestines!
and proceeded to stuff him full of rocks?
so he'd sink in the river!
That's enough reading!
No more stories!
The wolf is the villain of the story.
And I'm gonna make sure you
pay for eating my BROTHERS!
Shit!
Now I get the enemy Stan's target!
It was never after my body!
It wanted me to join the fantasy!
And I've already been
dragged into a story!
Excuse me. Good day, sir.
Is this the right way
to San Reimi Hospital?
Ask somebody else.
Oh.
Excuse me there.
Wait just a moment.
You are familiar with me, yes? I'm not.
Sorry, but I'm not from around here.
So I couldn't help you
even if I wanted to.
No, no, you've got it all wrong.
What I mean is you like me, yes?
It's written on your face
that you enjoy my work.
You were moved by it.
Allow me to introduce myself. I'm Go.
Oh, Van Gogh's self-portrait.
Just last night, with a razor
blade, I cut off my ear.
Hmm.
Yes, I see it in your eyes.
You were moved by me, correct?
Mother's coming back!
And when she gets here, she's gonna
make you pay with her scissors!
You better believe when Mother
shows up, you'll be screwed!
You bastard!
You want some of this, you bitch?!
Mama!
We're over here! Hey!
We're in here, Mama! Hey!
What did you say?
Mama!
Help us, please!
Bastards!
How dare you!
How dare you gobble up my darling kids!
I'll kill you!
More news on the fantasy hero stories.
The strange events, which first
started in Florida of the US,
are no longer exclusively characters
from fantasy books and cartoons.
We are now seeing various works
of fine art coming to life.
What does this mean for us?
Humankind's legacies, our
society's greatest treasures,
are vanishing before our eyes.
This damn stand,
its sole purpose is protecting the priest,
and the user doesn't care if the
whole world is collateral damage.
and the stand itself is invincible.
We need to defeat the user.
I think they're moving north.
Yes, I can sense them.
I don't know where they're
going, but they're moving fast.
They must be in a vehicle.
By the way, young sir,
how many self-portraits did he
paint over the course of his life?
Do you have any idea?
Stay away from me, or I'll kick your ass!
the answer is approximately 40 it said he
left them behind as a window into his soul
until he cut off his own ear and then when
he reached the ripe age of 37 years old
he committed suicide by
shooting himself with a pistol
you're a self-portrait as
well aren't you the one of
van gogh after he cut off
his own ear What did you say?
However, the truth of it is he
shot two bullets into his head.
He didn't die from the first one.
That's right,
the man needed one more bullet to put an
end to his pathetically miserable life.
This...
This enemy is...
Weather Forecast!
You need to go north!
Block off the highway 30 kilometers
ahead with a severe rainstorm.
Don't let any vehicles headed in
that direction go any farther!
Diver Drive transformed the inner part
of the door and fused it into the wall.
Nothing's getting through this door now.
Diver Drive!
My brothers are saved! Hooray!
It's just like the story!
Just like the story?
That's the only way things can play out!
Which means destroying these
jacked-up goats is impossible!
Use the Wall Diver
Drive! Phase through it!
Oh, damn.
I really did it.
It's the policemen from earlier.
Guess these guys got separated too.
In any case, I need to get
inside before it's too late.
Bring the rocks!
We need more rocks over here! Shit!
It's no use! Weather!
Hurry up and kill the
fucking stand user already!
What is this?
The enemy presence that
I felt heading north
just instantly started
moving towards the south.
No, could it be?
In the sky?
Flight 8250 to Key West
has departed on time.
Despite thunderstorms,
we will arrive at our destination
in approximately 45 minutes.
This sick-ass new power that
just awakened in me is great,
and its only weakness is
if I get attacked directly.
But now nobody's gonna be able
to catch up to me on this plane,
no matter who they are.
What an awesome feeling!
This sense of fulfillment's
really getting me fired up!
In reproduction,
to be born is also to be chosen,
and the chosen one,
even in their struggle against the other
sperms fighting for their chance of life,
is merely being raised up.
and protected by the ones beneath them.
The same can be said for those who
are drawn to me through destiny.
These individuals exist only to raise me
up towards my true goal
of attaining heaven.
Now that Jolene Cujo has
escaped and is headed my way,
she will just be another adversary for
me to step over on my path to ascension.
And you, sons of Dio,
you three shall protect me on our
journey to the land of Cape Canaveral.
That will be your reason
for existing and your
source of bliss until
the end of your days.
All I've done up till now is wander around
aimlessly as my life
spiraled into a total mess,
and I had no idea why.
But after today, I finally understand!
I've been existing through this
living hell for this ability!
Fuck drugs, I'll protect
that priest with my life!
And the best thing that came out of
this is my stand, Bohemian Ecstatic!
Thanks to this new power,
I get to watch the world that's
treated me like shit slowly
deteriorate as a society
falls into chaos and despair!
Damn it all.
I can't catch up.
If the enemy user is on a plane, it's
moving more than 400 kilometers per hour.
Even the largest hurricane recorded in
history only had a wind speed of 280.
There's not an atmospheric
phenomenon that can pursue the plane.
I let them get away!
Just one more bullet.
When I get hit with a second bullet,
the story will come to its end.
This is bad.
Don't you dare get any
closer to that pistol!
If you even try touching
it, I'll kill you!
Anesthesia!
Weather…
Ah, shiiiit!
Weather!
We're melting!
What the hell is this weather?
All right!
The big bad wolf is gonna drown today!
Just like the star of you! Hooray!
It's over.
Just as it should be.
I shall honor your sacrifice by
living a happy life in your stead.
According to experts,
the countries with the
most damages from this
fantasy hero incident
are the United States...
What can I do for you, Master Aladdin?
Since you freed me, I will
be your devoted servant.
With my power I can...
Stop mumbling to
yourself, you little brat!
Give me that book you're reading.
What is this?
I...
I can't breathe.
What more could you want from
me? Nothing. This is fine.
You've done well, thanks.
You're a really talented artist.
What did you make him draw? Hallweather?
I had Van Gogh here put his skills
to work and create a hero for me.
They have a story too.
Like most heroes, they have powers!
The power to defeat fantasy heroes
and return them all back to normal!
And this story can only end one way!
With the hero bringing
everything back to reality!
We're gonna return just
like the story describes!
Anastasia, there's no need to worry.
We're gonna return to
our bodies and hearts.
Hey, I said hey.
Come on, give me back my book.
Coming to you with an update.
It appears everything has
suddenly returned to normal.
All picture books, paintings,
comics, and films have been restored.
Mona Lisa, Snow White, Batman, and
even Tweety Bird have all returned.
Yet we have received reports that Pinocchio
has not reverted to its original place.
Are you asleep?
Was it too boring?
I don't see how though.
The story is so full of hope and fun.
Hey, what car are you
driving around in these days?
You get a new one?
You aren't driving the same
car from before, are you?
Romeo?
Jolene!
Just help me, Jolene!
Have you ever heard of
plea bargaining before?
Defendant Jolene Kujo is
sentenced to 15 years in... ROMEO!
Wait, I thought you were... But how?
Make this easy, Romeo.
Don't go anywhere near the phone.
Any phone for that matter.
Am I clear?
I would never do something like that.
Ever since that day, I've
been regretting what I did.
I can't forgive the sin
I've committed against you.
After losing you the way I did, I
finally realized just how stupid I was.
Jolene, I swear to God, I'm
so sorry for betraying you.
How will you ever forgive?
Shh, shh.
You don't have to say a word, Romeo.
You're the only one in this world for me.
I see it now.
It has to be you, baby.
I tried to visit you in jail,
too, but they didn't let me.
Oh, Romeo.
Poor, poor Romeo.
Have you always been this pitiful?
Listen, just forget about the hit-and-run.
I don't care about it anymore.
I don't hate you, and
I don't hold a grudge,
now that I know the wreck was
all part of a plot against me.
Romeo, I came here because I
need to ask you for a favor.
I want some money and a car.
There is an important place I need to be.
Yeah, sure, but I only have a grand on me.
And here, these are my
keys. This is plenty.
Thank you, Romeo.
But if the police come by, don't
say anything. Promise me. Oh, man.
Jolene, I plan on turning myself in so
that I can prove you were always innocent.
So please, come back to me!
Awesome you got the keys to his car?
Hello yes my name is Romeo
Jazz and I live in Palm Beach.
Is this the police?
I'd like to report an escaped convict.
Yes her name is Jolene Cujo.
Like I thought.
Aren't you glad I told
you to plant one of my
stickers on that bendejo
and split it in two?
He's already calling the cops.
That snitch.
No!
You're mistaken.
She never came to my house.
She couldn't have.
I'm calling in to report because
I just received a call from her.
Yes, that's all.
She was begging for money,
but I turned her down.
I think she said she
was headed for Mexico.
Of course.
If she calls again, I'll let you know.
Yes, goodbye.
Well damn, look at that.
He didn't betray you after all.
If only she could forgive me one day.
I'd do anything for her.
Hey, check it out!
Isn't it cool?
Your ex is loaded!
What do you think he gave you?
Sure his car keys are
here, but that's not all.
Look at that thing!
Are we really allowed to take that one?
I want to try steering.
Flying the real thing must be Way different
from just reading about it in books.
Romeo, you've changed.
I believe you.
But let's peel it off anyway.
Just in case.
Let's get out of here.
If we take the helicopter, we
can get there in a few hours.
Although you think I cope
My head is filled with hope
Of some place
other than here
Although you think I smile
Inside and all the while
I'm wondering about my destiny?
I'm thinking
about all the
things I'd like
to do in my life.
I'm a dreamer,
a distant dreamer,
dreaming for
all from today.
Father, I understand that my
mission will be protecting you,
But before that, will
you please open my eyes?
You see one of my eyelids.
It keeps on drooping down,
and it doesn't go back up.
It only goes up sometimes.
Thank you.